A frequently used to an agent is search.
This lesson is going to dive into how agent search is different from standard search,
and how to use it.
Let's try it out.
Alright, so before diving into what an agent search does, let's understand how an agent
might use it.
In a zero-shot learning, an agent would receive a prompt, and would produce an answer based
on its static weights of the model.
The powerful as it proven to be, there are many limitations to this process.
First, the data around us is dynamic, so it couldn't, for instance, ask about the scores
from the game last night.
Secondly, in many use cases, we would want to know the sources of the information provided
in the result.
This can reduce hallucinations and smooth the friction of this human computer interaction.
Looking at the slide, we can see the prompt is received by the agent, which then decides
to call the search tool, then the information found is returned to the agent.
Now, let me show you what happens inside.
This is an example of a very basic search tool implementation.
Let's go over it step-by-step.
If the agent decides, it will send a query to the search tool.
The first step would work on understanding the question and divide it to sub-questions
it needed.
This is an important step, because it can handle complex queries.
And for each sub-query, the search tool will have to find the best source, choosing from
multiple integrations.
For example, if an agent would ask, how is the weather in San Francisco?
The search tool should use a weather API for best results.
The job doesn't end with finding the correct source.
The search tool would then have to extract only the relevant information to the sub-query.
A basic implementation of this can be achieved through a process of chunking the source and
run a quick vector search to retrieve the top-case chunks.
After retrieving the data from its source, the search tool would then score the results
and filter out the less relevant information.
Okay, so let's test it out.
Okay, so first let's import some libraries and do the initial connection to the search tool.
Here we loaded the Tavili API key from the environment variables.
And then we create the Tavili client, which we imported from the Tavili library.
Alright, so after creating the initial connection, let's test it out.
Here I'm going to run a search, asking about and videos in your black hole GPU.
And let's see what's the answer.
Alright, so as you can see there's a pretty simple answer, but very accurate.
Okay, so let's do a simple example to see the difference between a regular search tool.
And an agent search tool.
I'm going to create a simple query about the weather in a certain location.
Feel free to change the location to your location.
I'm going to do it with San Francisco.
So the query is what is the current weather in San Francisco?
So they traveled there today.
Now let's try to attempt it with regular search.
Here I'm going to import the Dr. Go search.
I'll try to run a regular search and get the links.
The links that might lead me to the answer.
Okay, so as you can see, we did get the results, but it's not what the agent need.
Now we're going to have to get some answers from these results.
Let's do that.
Okay, so now we're going to create a function that can scrape the data from the first URL.
We're going to use beautiful soup to extract the HTML.
As you can see, that's a beautiful output.
And if you want, you can keep scrolling down.
But let's try to clear it up.
Okay, to clear it out, I'm going to use some parsing.
I'm going to extract the headers and some content.
I'm going to strip it down and use join to get the text.
As you can see, the output is much, much better, but still not concise enough.
Okay, after seeing this, let's try to run it using the agent search tool.
We're going to do the same query and code to build it together as the results.
As you can see, we got a simple JSON.
We have a lot of information about the weather in San Francisco.
Let's clear it out so we can see a parameter JSON.
Okay, now we'll parse it and highlight the JSON so we can see it clearly.
As you can see, this is not the answer I would want to see as a human.
But this is the exact answer an agent would want, a structured data.
Okay, I'm going to load the sample from Google search, so you can see the difference here.
I get exactly what I want as a human.
A nice image showing me the temperature, the humidity, the wind, but not unnecessary data.
That's exactly the difference between what a human need and what an agent need.
Okay, that was an introduction to agent search.
In the next lesson, Harrison will discuss persistence and streaming.